{"problemsArray": [
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(2x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(4x^2 + 7x + 1)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 11)(4x^2 + 7x + 1)/2(2x + 9)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 11)/(2x + 9)] / [(2x + 8)/(4x^2 + 7x + 1)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 11)/(2x + 9)] * [(4x^2 + 7x + 1)/(2x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 11)/(2x + 9)] * [(4x^2 + 7x + 1)/2(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(4x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(2x^2 + 15x + 17)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 11)(2x^2 + 15x + 17)/4(x + 2)(4x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 11)/(4x + 8)] / [(4x + 11)/(2x^2 + 15x + 17)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 11)/(4x + 8)] * [(2x^2 + 15x + 17)/(4x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 11)/4(x + 2)] * [(2x^2 + 15x + 17)/(4x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/(2x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(2x^2 + 15x + 9)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 8)(2x^2 + 15x + 9)/(2x + 5)(4x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 8)/(2x + 5)] / [(4x + 1)/(2x^2 + 15x + 9)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 8)/(2x + 5)] * [(2x^2 + 15x + 9)/(4x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 8)/(2x + 5)] * [(2x^2 + 15x + 9)/(4x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(4x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/(3x^2 + 10x + 1)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 5)(3x^2 + 10x + 1)/(4x + 11)(4x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 5)/(4x + 11)] / [(4x + 9)/(3x^2 + 10x + 1)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 5)/(4x + 11)] * [(3x^2 + 10x + 1)/(4x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 5)/(4x + 11)] * [(3x^2 + 10x + 1)/(4x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 8)/(x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x^2 + 10x + 4)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 8)(x^2 + 10x + 4)/(x + 5)(4x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 8)/(x + 5)] / [(4x + 1)/(x^2 + 10x + 4)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 8)/(x + 5)] * [(x^2 + 10x + 4)/(4x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 8)/(x + 5)] * [(x^2 + 10x + 4)/(4x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(x^2 + 15x + 17)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 11)(x^2 + 15x + 17)/(x + 9)(4x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 11)/(x + 9)] / [(4x + 11)/(x^2 + 15x + 17)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 11)/(x + 9)] * [(x^2 + 15x + 17)/(4x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 11)/(x + 9)] * [(x^2 + 15x + 17)/(4x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(2x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(x^2 + 10x + 13)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 7)(x^2 + 10x + 13)/(2x + 9)(2x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 7)/(2x + 9)] / [(2x + 11)/(x^2 + 10x + 13)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 7)/(2x + 9)] * [(x^2 + 10x + 13)/(2x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 7)/(2x + 9)] * [(x^2 + 10x + 13)/(2x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(2x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(x^2 + 10x + 20)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 1)(x^2 + 10x + 20)/4(x + 2)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 1)/(2x + 4)] / [(2x + 8)/(x^2 + 10x + 20)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 1)/(2x + 4)] * [(x^2 + 10x + 20)/(2x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 1)/2(x + 2)] * [(x^2 + 10x + 20)/2(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(4x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(6x^2 + 13x + 3)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 3)(6x^2 + 13x + 3)/(4x + 9)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 3)/(4x + 9)] / [(x + 3)/(6x^2 + 13x + 3)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 3)/(4x + 9)] * [(6x^2 + 13x + 3)/(x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 3)/(4x + 9)] * [(6x^2 + 13x + 3)/(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 10)/(3x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(x^2 + 10x + 2)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 10)(x^2 + 10x + 2)/(3x + 5)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 10)/(3x + 5)] / [(x + 3)/(x^2 + 10x + 2)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 10)/(3x + 5)] * [(x^2 + 10x + 2)/(x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 10)/(3x + 5)] * [(x^2 + 10x + 2)/(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(4x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(2x^2 + 8x + 4)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 2)(x^2 + 4x + 2)/(2x + 1)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 2)/(4x + 2)] / [(2x + 3)/(2x^2 + 8x + 4)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 2)/(4x + 2)] * [(2x^2 + 8x + 4)/(2x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 2)/2(2x + 1)] * [2(x^2 + 4x + 2)/(2x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(4x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(5x^2 + 15x + 7)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(5x^2 + 15x + 7)/8(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 2)/(4x + 8)] / [(2x + 10)/(5x^2 + 15x + 7)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 2)/(4x + 8)] * [(5x^2 + 15x + 7)/(2x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[1/4] * [(5x^2 + 15x + 7)/2(x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 2)/(2x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(x^2 + 7x + 3)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 1)(x^2 + 7x + 3)/(2x + 1)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 2)/(2x + 1)] / [(x + 3)/(x^2 + 7x + 3)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 2)/(2x + 1)] * [(x^2 + 7x + 3)/(x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 1)/(2x + 1)] * [(x^2 + 7x + 3)/(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 6)/(2x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 3)/(x^2 + 11x + 1)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 3)(x^2 + 11x + 1)/3(2x + 1)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 6)/(2x + 1)] / [(3x + 3)/(x^2 + 11x + 1)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 6)/(2x + 1)] * [(x^2 + 11x + 1)/(3x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 3)/(2x + 1)] * [(x^2 + 11x + 1)/3(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(2x + 10),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(x^2 + 7x + 9)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x^2 + 7x + 9)/2(4x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 5)/(2x + 10)] / [(4x + 3)/(x^2 + 7x + 9)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 5)/(2x + 10)] * [(x^2 + 7x + 9)/(4x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[1/2] * [(x^2 + 7x + 9)/(4x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(2x^2 + 6x + 2)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 11)(x + 9)/2(x + 11)(x^2 + 3x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 11)/(x + 11)] * [(x + 9)/(2x^2 + 6x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 11)/(x + 11)] * [(x + 9)/2(x^2 + 3x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(3x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 8)/(2x^2 + 13x + 1)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "4(2x + 11)(x + 2)/3(x + 1)(2x^2 + 13x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 11)/(3x + 3)] * [(4x + 8)/(2x^2 + 13x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 11)/3(x + 1)] * [4(x + 2)/(2x^2 + 13x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(2x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/(5x^2 + 11x + 1)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 3)(4x + 5)/(2x + 11)(5x^2 + 11x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 9)/(2x + 11)] * [(4x + 5)/(5x^2 + 11x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x + 3)/(2x + 11)] * [(4x + 5)/(5x^2 + 11x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(4x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/(6x^2 + 15x + 2)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 5)(4x + 5)/(4x + 7)(6x^2 + 15x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 10)/(4x + 7)] * [(4x + 5)/(6x^2 + 15x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 5)/(4x + 7)] * [(4x + 5)/(6x^2 + 15x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(3x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(2x^2 + 15x + 24)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 1)(x + 11)/(3x + 2)(2x^2 + 15x + 24)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 1)/(3x + 2)] * [(x + 11)/(2x^2 + 15x + 24)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 1)/(3x + 2)] * [(x + 11)/(2x^2 + 15x + 24)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 2)/(5x^2 + 14x + 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 2)(x + 1)/(x + 9)(5x^2 + 14x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 2)/(x + 9)] * [(2x + 2)/(5x^2 + 14x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 2)/(x + 9)] * [2(x + 1)/(5x^2 + 14x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(x^2 + 9x + 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 11)(x + 11)/(x + 8)(x^2 + 9x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 11)/(x + 8)] * [(x + 11)/(x^2 + 9x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 11)/(x + 8)] * [(x + 11)/(x^2 + 9x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/(2x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(2x^2 + 12x + 2)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 9)(x + 3)/2(2x + 7)(x^2 + 6x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 9)/(2x + 7)] * [(x + 3)/(2x^2 + 12x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 9)/(2x + 7)] * [(x + 3)/2(x^2 + 6x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(2x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(x^2 + 10x + 11)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 11)(3x + 10)/2(x + 4)(x^2 + 10x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 11)/(2x + 8)] * [(3x + 10)/(x^2 + 10x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 11)/2(x + 4)] * [(3x + 10)/(x^2 + 10x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(2x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(2x^2 + 14x + 16)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 1)(3x + 10)/4(x + 3)(x^2 + 7x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 1)/(2x + 6)] * [(3x + 10)/(2x^2 + 14x + 16)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 1)/2(x + 3)] * [(3x + 10)/2(x^2 + 7x + 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 6)/(2x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(3x^2 + 14x + 2)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 2)(x + 7)/2(x + 4)(3x^2 + 14x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 6)/(2x + 8)] * [(x + 7)/(3x^2 + 14x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x + 2)/2(x + 4)] * [(x + 7)/(3x^2 + 14x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(2x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(x^2 + 8x + 2)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 3)(3x + 10)/(2x + 7)(x^2 + 8x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 3)/(2x + 7)] * [(3x + 10)/(x^2 + 8x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 3)/(2x + 7)] * [(3x + 10)/(x^2 + 8x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 4)/(3x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(3x^2 + 12x + 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "8(x + 1)(x + 5)/(3x + 11)(3x^2 + 12x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 4)/(3x + 11)] * [(2x + 10)/(3x^2 + 12x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(x + 1)/(3x + 11)] * [2(x + 5)/(3x^2 + 12x + 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 1)/(2x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 8)/(2x^2 + 15x + 19)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 1)(x + 8)/2(x + 3)(2x^2 + 15x + 19)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 1)/(2x + 6)] * [(x + 8)/(2x^2 + 15x + 19)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 1)/2(x + 3)] * [(x + 8)/(2x^2 + 15x + 19)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(3x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(x^2 + 8x + 10)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 10)(3x + 7)/(3x + 11)(x^2 + 8x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 10)/(3x + 11)] * [(3x + 7)/(x^2 + 8x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 10)/(3x + 11)] * [(3x + 7)/(x^2 + 8x + 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(2x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/(2x + 2)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 11)(x + 1)/(x - 1)(3x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 11)/(2x - 2)] / [(3x + 8)/(2x + 2)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 11)/(2x - 2)] * [(2x + 2)/(3x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 11)/2(x - 1)] * [2(x + 1)/(3x + 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 5)/(4x - 6),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(4x + 8)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x - 5)(x + 2)/(2x - 3)(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 5)/(4x - 6)] / [(2x + 1)/(4x + 8)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 5)/(4x - 6)] * [(4x + 8)/(2x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 5)/2(2x - 3)] * [4(x + 2)/(2x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(2x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(4x + 3)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 3)(4x + 3)/2(x + 4)(3x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 3)/(2x + 8)] / [(3x + 5)/(4x + 3)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 3)/(2x + 8)] * [(4x + 3)/(3x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 3)/2(x + 4)] * [(4x + 3)/(3x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/(2x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(4x + 6)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x + 7)(2x + 3)/(2x + 1)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 7)/(2x + 1)] / [(2x + 5)/(4x + 6)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 7)/(2x + 1)] * [(4x + 6)/(2x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 7)/(2x + 1)] * [2(2x + 3)/(2x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 10)/(3x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(3x + 9)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 10)/(3x - 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 10)/(3x - 1)] / [(3x + 9)/(3x + 9)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 10)/(3x - 1)] * [(3x + 9)/(3x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 10)/(3x - 1)] * [1]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 5)/(2x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(x + 11)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 5)(x + 11)/2(x + 2)(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 5)/(2x + 4)] / [(x + 5)/(x + 11)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 5)/(2x + 4)] * [(x + 11)/(x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 5)/2(x + 2)] * [(x + 11)/(x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(4x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 6)/(2x + 1)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 3)(2x + 1)/2(2x - 1)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 9)/(4x - 2)] / [(3x + 6)/(2x + 1)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 9)/(4x - 2)] * [(2x + 1)/(3x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x + 3)/2(2x - 1)] * [(2x + 1)/3(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 8)/(3x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(2x + 7)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "4(x + 2)(2x + 7)/(3x - 2)(3x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 8)/(3x - 2)] / [(3x + 4)/(2x + 7)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 8)/(3x - 2)] * [(2x + 7)/(3x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(x + 2)/(3x - 2)] * [(2x + 7)/(3x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 8)/(3x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/(4x + 5)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "4(x - 2)(4x + 5)/3(x - 1)(4x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 8)/(3x - 3)] / [(4x + 7)/(4x + 5)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 8)/(3x - 3)] * [(4x + 5)/(4x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(x - 2)/3(x - 1)] * [(4x + 5)/(4x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/(4x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(x + 7)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 9)(x + 7)/2(2x + 3)(3x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 9)/(4x + 6)] / [(3x + 5)/(x + 7)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 9)/(4x + 6)] * [(x + 7)/(3x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 9)/2(2x + 3)] * [(x + 7)/(3x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(x - 8),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/(x + 10)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 5)(x + 10)/(x - 8)(4x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 5)/(x - 8)] / [(4x + 5)/(x + 10)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 5)/(x - 8)] * [(x + 10)/(4x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 5)/(x - 8)] * [(x + 10)/(4x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 1)/(3x - 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(3x + 3)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(4x - 1)(x + 1)/(3x - 5)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 1)/(3x - 5)] / [(x + 3)/(3x + 3)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 1)/(3x - 5)] * [(3x + 3)/(x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x - 1)/(3x - 5)] * [3(x + 1)/(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(2x + 10)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x + 3)(x + 5)/(x + 6)(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 3)/(x + 6)] / [(3x + 7)/(2x + 10)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 3)/(x + 6)] * [(2x + 10)/(3x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 3)/(x + 6)] * [2(x + 5)/(3x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 2)/(x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/(x + 4)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x - 1)(x + 4)/(x + 6)(4x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 2)/(x + 6)] / [(4x + 7)/(x + 4)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 2)/(x + 6)] * [(x + 4)/(4x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x - 1)/(x + 6)] * [(x + 4)/(4x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 10)/(3x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(x + 7)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 10)(x + 7)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 10)/(3x + 2)] / [(3x + 5)/(x + 7)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 10)/(3x + 2)] * [(x + 7)/(3x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 10)/(3x + 2)] * [(x + 7)/(3x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(2x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 10)/(x + 5)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 7)(x + 5)/2(2x - 1)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 7)/(2x - 1)] / [(4x + 10)/(x + 5)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 7)/(2x - 1)] * [(x + 5)/(4x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 7)/(2x - 1)] * [(x + 5)/2(2x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 8)/(3x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/(x + 10)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x - 4)(x + 10)/3(x + 1)(4x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 8)/(3x + 3)] / [(4x + 9)/(x + 10)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 8)/(3x + 3)] * [(x + 10)/(4x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 4)/3(x + 1)] * [(x + 10)/(4x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 4)/(3x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(2x + 10)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "4(x + 1)(x + 5)/(3x + 8)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 4)/(3x + 8)] / [(2x + 8)/(2x + 10)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 4)/(3x + 8)] * [(2x + 10)/(2x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(x + 1)/(3x + 8)] * [(x + 5)/(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 9)/(2x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(2x + 8)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(x - 3)(x + 4)/(x - 1)(3x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 9)/(2x - 2)] / [(3x + 10)/(2x + 8)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 9)/(2x - 2)] * [(2x + 8)/(3x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x - 3)/2(x - 1)] * [2(x + 4)/(3x + 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 1)/(2x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 10)/(4x + 3)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x - 1)(4x + 3)/2(2x - 1)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 1)/(2x - 1)] / [(4x + 10)/(4x + 3)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 1)/(2x - 1)] * [(4x + 3)/(4x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 1)/(2x - 1)] * [(4x + 3)/2(2x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(4x - 8),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(x + 5)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 11)(x + 5)/4(x - 2)(x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 11)/(4x - 8)] / [(x + 7)/(x + 5)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 11)/(4x - 8)] * [(x + 5)/(x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 11)/4(x - 2)] * [(x + 5)/(x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 5)/(2x - 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(3x + 6)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(3x - 5)(x + 2)/(2x - 5)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 5)/(2x - 5)] / [(x + 1)/(3x + 6)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 5)/(2x - 5)] * [(3x + 6)/(x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 5)/(2x - 5)] * [3(x + 2)/(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(2x + 3)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 5)(2x + 3)/(x + 5)(2x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 5)/(x + 5)] / [(2x + 9)/(2x + 3)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 5)/(x + 5)] * [(2x + 3)/(2x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 5)/(x + 5)] * [(2x + 3)/(2x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 2)/(2x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 8)/(3x + 11)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 1)(3x + 11)/(x + 2)(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 2)/(2x + 4)] / [(x + 8)/(3x + 11)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 2)/(2x + 4)] * [(3x + 11)/(x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 1)/(x + 2)] * [(3x + 11)/(x + 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(4x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 6)/(4x + 4)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(4x + 11)(x + 1)/(4x - 1)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 11)/(4x - 1)] / [(2x + 6)/(4x + 4)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 11)/(4x - 1)] * [(4x + 4)/(2x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 11)/(4x - 1)] * [2(x + 1)/(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(3x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 10)/(x + 5)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 3)(x + 5)/(3x + 5)(x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 3)/(3x + 5)] / [(x + 10)/(x + 5)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 3)/(3x + 5)] * [(x + 5)/(x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 3)/(3x + 5)] * [(x + 5)/(x + 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(3x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/(4x + 11)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 4)(4x + 11)/(3x + 2)(4x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 8)/(3x + 2)] / [(4x + 7)/(4x + 11)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 8)/(3x + 2)] * [(4x + 11)/(4x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 4)/(3x + 2)] * [(4x + 11)/(4x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 4)/(x - 8),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(x + 5)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 4)(x + 5)/2(x - 8)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 4)/(x - 8)] / [(2x + 8)/(x + 5)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 4)/(x - 8)] * [(x + 5)/(2x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 4)/(x - 8)] * [(x + 5)/2(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 7)/(4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(2x + 2)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(4x - 7)(x + 1)/(4x + 1)(2x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 7)/(4x + 1)] / [(2x + 9)/(2x + 2)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 7)/(4x + 1)] * [(2x + 2)/(2x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x - 7)/(4x + 1)] * [2(x + 1)/(2x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(4x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 10)/(2x + 5)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 7)(2x + 5)/(4x - 7)(x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 7)/(4x - 7)] / [(x + 10)/(2x + 5)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 7)/(4x - 7)] * [(2x + 5)/(x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 7)/(4x - 7)] * [(2x + 5)/(x + 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 6)/(4x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x + 9)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 2)(x + 9)/(4x - 3)(4x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 6)/(4x - 3)] / [(4x + 1)/(x + 9)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 6)/(4x - 3)] * [(x + 9)/(4x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x + 2)/(4x - 3)] * [(x + 9)/(4x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(2x + 11)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 7)(2x + 11)/(4x + 1)(4x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 7)/(4x + 1)] / [(4x + 3)/(2x + 11)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 7)/(4x + 1)] * [(2x + 11)/(4x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 7)/(4x + 1)] * [(2x + 11)/(4x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 7)/(2x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(3x + 11)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 7)(3x + 11)/2(x - 1)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 7)/(2x - 2)] / [(x + 2)/(3x + 11)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 7)/(2x - 2)] * [(3x + 11)/(x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 7)/2(x - 1)] * [(3x + 11)/(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 3)/(x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/(3x + 8)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(x - 1)(3x + 8)/(x + 7)(4x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 3)/(x + 7)] / [(4x + 5)/(3x + 8)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 3)/(x + 7)] * [(3x + 8)/(4x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x - 1)/(x + 7)] * [(3x + 8)/(4x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(4x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(2x + 5)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 9)(2x + 5)/(4x - 1)(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 9)/(4x - 1)] / [(3x + 7)/(2x + 5)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 9)/(4x - 1)] * [(2x + 5)/(3x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 9)/(4x - 1)] * [(2x + 5)/(3x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 6)/(4x - 10),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(4x + 8)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x - 6)(x + 2)/(2x - 5)(2x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 6)/(4x - 10)] / [(2x + 11)/(4x + 8)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 6)/(4x - 10)] * [(4x + 8)/(2x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 6)/2(2x - 5)] * [4(x + 2)/(2x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(4x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(3x + 4)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 3)(3x + 4)/2(2x + 1)(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 3)/(4x + 2)] / [(x + 5)/(3x + 4)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 3)/(4x + 2)] * [(3x + 4)/(x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 3)/2(2x + 1)] * [(3x + 4)/(x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(3x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 8)/(3x + 1)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 10)(3x + 1)/4(3x - 2)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 10)/(3x - 2)] / [(4x + 8)/(3x + 1)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 10)/(3x - 2)] * [(3x + 1)/(4x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 10)/(3x - 2)] * [(3x + 1)/4(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 3)/(3x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 3)/(2x + 2)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x - 3)/9(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 3)/(3x + 6)] / [(3x + 3)/(2x + 2)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 3)/(3x + 6)] * [(2x + 2)/(3x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 3)/3(x + 2)] * [2/3]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(3x + 6)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(4x + 11)(x + 2)/(x + 5)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 11)/(x + 5)] / [(x + 3)/(3x + 6)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 11)/(x + 5)] * [(3x + 6)/(x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 11)/(x + 5)] * [3(x + 2)/(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 6)/(2x - 9),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 8)/(2x + 7)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(x - 2)(2x + 7)/4(2x - 9)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 6)/(2x - 9)] / [(4x + 8)/(2x + 7)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 6)/(2x - 9)] * [(2x + 7)/(4x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x - 2)/(2x - 9)] * [(2x + 7)/4(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 6)/(x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(3x + 5)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 2)(3x + 5)/2(x - 4)(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 6)/(x - 4)] / [(2x + 10)/(3x + 5)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 6)/(x - 4)] * [(3x + 5)/(2x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x + 2)/(x - 4)] * [(3x + 5)/2(x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 10)/(x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 3)/(3x + 11)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x - 5)(3x + 11)/3(x + 8)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 10)/(x + 8)] / [(3x + 3)/(3x + 11)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 10)/(x + 8)] * [(3x + 11)/(3x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 5)/(x + 8)] * [(3x + 11)/3(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 7)/(x + 10),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 2)/(3x + 8)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x - 7)(3x + 8)/2(x + 10)(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 7)/(x + 10)] / [(4x + 2)/(3x + 8)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 7)/(x + 10)] * [(3x + 8)/(4x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 7)/(x + 10)] * [(3x + 8)/2(2x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 8)/(x - 8),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(3x + 3)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "12(x - 2)(x + 1)/(x - 8)(x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 8)/(x - 8)] / [(x + 7)/(3x + 3)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 8)/(x - 8)] * [(3x + 3)/(x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(x - 2)/(x - 8)] * [3(x + 1)/(x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(4x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 3)/(2x + 8)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "4(x + 4)(x + 4)/3(4x - 7)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 8)/(4x - 7)] / [(3x + 3)/(2x + 8)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 8)/(4x - 7)] * [(2x + 8)/(3x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 4)/(4x - 7)] * [2(x + 4)/3(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 1)/(3x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(3x + 11)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 1)(3x + 11)/(3x - 2)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 1)/(3x - 2)] / [(2x + 3)/(3x + 11)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 1)/(3x - 2)] * [(3x + 11)/(2x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 1)/(3x - 2)] * [(3x + 11)/(2x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 3)/(x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(3x + 1)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x - 3)(3x + 1)/(x + 1)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 3)/(x + 1)] / [(2x + 5)/(3x + 1)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 3)/(x + 1)] * [(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 3)/(x + 1)] * [(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 5)/(2x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(2x + 1)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 5)(2x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 5)/(2x + 5)] / [(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 5)/(2x + 5)] * [(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 5)/(2x + 5)] * [(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 2)/(4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(x + 7)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 1)/(4x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 2)/(4x + 1)] / [(x + 7)/(x + 7)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 2)/(4x + 1)] * [(x + 7)/(x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 1)/(4x + 1)] * [1]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 1)/(4x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(3x + 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(2x - 1)(x + 3)/4(x + 2)(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 1)/(4x + 8)] * [(3x + 9)/(3x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 1)/4(x + 2)] * [3(x + 3)/(3x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(x - 6),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(x + 4)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 4)(x + 7)/(x - 6)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 4)/(x - 6)] * [(x + 7)/(x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 4)/(x - 6)] * [(x + 7)/(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/(x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/(4x + 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 5)(2x + 7)/(x + 9)(4x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 5)/(x + 9)] * [(2x + 7)/(4x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 5)/(x + 9)] * [(2x + 7)/(4x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(4x + 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 3)(3x + 10)/(x + 4)(4x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 3)/(x + 4)] * [(3x + 10)/(4x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 3)/(x + 4)] * [(3x + 10)/(4x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 4)/(2x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(4x + 4)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 2)(4x + 3)/2(2x - 3)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 4)/(2x - 3)] * [(4x + 3)/(4x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 2)/(2x - 3)] * [(4x + 3)/4(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 10)/(4x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/(x + 1)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x - 5)(4x + 5)/(4x - 3)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 10)/(4x - 3)] * [(4x + 5)/(x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x - 5)/(4x - 3)] * [(4x + 5)/(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(3x - 10),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 2)/(3x + 1)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(3x + 11)(x + 1)/(3x - 10)(3x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 11)/(3x - 10)] * [(2x + 2)/(3x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 11)/(3x - 10)] * [2(x + 1)/(3x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(2x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(4x + 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 11)(x + 5)/2(x - 1)(4x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 11)/(2x - 2)] * [(x + 5)/(4x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 11)/2(x - 1)] * [(x + 5)/(4x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 6)/(3x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 10)/(4x + 6)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 6)(x + 10)/2(3x - 2)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 6)/(3x - 2)] * [(x + 10)/(4x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 6)/(3x - 2)] * [(x + 10)/2(2x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 4)/(x + 2)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x + 5)/(x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 5)/(x + 11)] * [(2x + 4)/(x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 5)/(x + 11)] * [2]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 5)/(x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/(3x + 2)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 5)/(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 5)/(x + 8)] * [(3x + 2)/(3x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 5)/(x + 8)] * [1]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 4)/(x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(x + 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x - 4)(2x + 3)/(x - 2)(x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 4)/(x - 2)] * [(4x + 6)/(x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 4)/(x - 2)] * [2(2x + 3)/(x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 8)/(4x - 9),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(3x + 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x - 4)(x + 9)/(4x - 9)(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 8)/(4x - 9)] * [(x + 9)/(3x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 4)/(4x - 9)] * [(x + 9)/(3x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 6)/(4x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(x + 3)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x - 3)(4x + 1)/(4x - 7)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 6)/(4x - 7)] * [(4x + 1)/(x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x - 3)/(4x - 7)] * [(4x + 1)/(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 2)/(3x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(x + 3)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x - 1)(x + 7)/(3x + 11)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 2)/(3x + 11)] * [(x + 7)/(x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x - 1)/(3x + 11)] * [(x + 7)/(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(x + 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 3)(2x + 9)/(x + 4)(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 9)/(x + 4)] * [(2x + 9)/(x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x + 3)/(x + 4)] * [(2x + 9)/(x + 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(3x + 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 3)(x + 1)/(4x + 1)(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 3)/(4x + 1)] * [(x + 1)/(3x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 3)/(4x + 1)] * [(x + 1)/(3x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 1)/(x - 10),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/(x + 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x - 1)(3x + 8)/(x - 10)(x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 1)/(x - 10)] * [(3x + 8)/(x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 1)/(x - 10)] * [(3x + 8)/(x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 8)/(2x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(4x + 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "4(x + 2)(x + 2)/(2x + 1)(4x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 8)/(2x + 1)] * [(x + 2)/(4x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(x + 2)/(2x + 1)] * [(x + 2)/(4x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 8)/(2x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(2x + 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 2)/(2x - 7)(2x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 8)/(2x - 7)] * [(x + 2)/(2x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 8)/(2x - 7)] * [(x + 2)/(2x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 7)/(3x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 2)/(4x + 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(3x - 7)(2x + 1)/3(x + 1)(4x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 7)/(3x + 3)] * [(4x + 2)/(4x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 7)/3(x + 1)] * [2(2x + 1)/(4x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 4)/(2x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(2x + 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 2)(2x + 11)/2(x + 2)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 4)/(2x + 4)] * [(2x + 11)/(2x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 2)/(x + 2)] * [(2x + 11)/2(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 5)/(2x - 10),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(2x + 6)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x - 5)(2x + 3)/4(x - 5)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 5)/(2x - 10)] * [(2x + 3)/(2x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 5)/2(x - 5)] * [(2x + 3)/2(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 5)/(2x - 9),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(3x + 11)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x - 5)(3x + 5)/(2x - 9)(3x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 5)/(2x - 9)] * [(3x + 5)/(3x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 5)/(2x - 9)] * [(3x + 5)/(3x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 6)/(x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(2x + 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x - 2)(2x + 3)/(x + 4)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 6)/(x + 4)] * [(4x + 6)/(2x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x - 2)/(x + 4)] * [(2x + 3)/(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 2)/(3x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(2x + 11)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x + 3)/(2x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 2)/(3x - 2)] * [(4x + 6)/(2x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[1] * [2(2x + 3)/(2x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 9)/(2x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 6)/(x + 10)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(2x - 9)(x + 2)/(2x - 7)(x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 9)/(2x - 7)] * [(3x + 6)/(x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 9)/(2x - 7)] * [3(x + 2)/(x + 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(2x - 6),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(4x + 3)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 10)(2x + 3)/(x - 3)(4x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 10)/(2x - 6)] * [(4x + 6)/(4x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 10)/2(x - 3)] * [2(2x + 3)/(4x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 4)/(2x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(3x + 3)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 4)(2x + 5)/3(2x + 1)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 4)/(2x + 1)] * [(2x + 5)/(3x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 4)/(2x + 1)] * [(2x + 5)/3(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 10)/(x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(3x + 4)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x - 10)(x + 5)/(x - 4)(3x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 10)/(x - 4)] * [(2x + 10)/(3x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 10)/(x - 4)] * [2(x + 5)/(3x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 8)/(3x - 9),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(3x + 10)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "4(x - 2)(4x + 3)/3(x - 3)(3x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 8)/(3x - 9)] * [(4x + 3)/(3x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(x - 2)/3(x - 3)] * [(4x + 3)/(3x + 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(4x - 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(2x + 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x + 3)(x + 9)/(4x - 5)(2x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 6)/(4x - 5)] * [(x + 9)/(2x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x + 3)/(4x - 5)] * [(x + 9)/(2x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(2x + 5)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(2x + 11)(x + 3)/(4x + 1)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 11)/(4x + 1)] * [(3x + 9)/(2x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 11)/(4x + 1)] * [3(x + 3)/(2x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/(3x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(4x + 6)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 7)(x + 4)/(3x - 1)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 7)/(3x - 1)] * [(2x + 8)/(4x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 7)/(3x - 1)] * [(x + 4)/(2x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(3x - 6),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(x + 10)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 3)(x + 5)/3(x - 2)(x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 3)/(3x - 6)] * [(x + 5)/(x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 3)/3(x - 2)] * [(x + 5)/(x + 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(4x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(3x + 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 5)(x + 5)/6(x + 2)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 5)/(4x + 8)] * [(2x + 10)/(3x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 5)/4(x + 2)] * [2(x + 5)/3(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 3)/(2x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(x + 11)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x - 3)(x + 9)/2(x + 3)(x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 3)/(2x + 6)] * [(x + 9)/(x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 3)/2(x + 3)] * [(x + 9)/(x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 10)/(3x - 9),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 5)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x - 5)(x + 1)/3(x - 3)(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 10)/(3x - 9)] * [(x + 1)/(x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 5)/3(x - 3)] * [(x + 1)/(x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(3x + 6)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "4(x + 5)(2x + 3)/3(x - 4)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 10)/(x - 4)] * [(4x + 6)/(3x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 5)/(x - 4)] * [2(2x + 3)/3(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 7)/(4x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(4x + 6)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 7)(x + 9)/4(2x - 1)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 7)/(4x - 2)] * [(x + 9)/(4x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 7)/2(2x - 1)] * [(x + 9)/2(2x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(3x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(4x + 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(3x + 11)(2x + 3)/(3x - 7)(4x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 11)/(3x - 7)] * [(4x + 6)/(4x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 11)/(3x - 7)] * [2(2x + 3)/(4x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(3x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(x + 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 3)(3x + 4)/(3x - 7)(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 9)/(3x - 7)] * [(3x + 4)/(x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x + 3)/(3x - 7)] * [(3x + 4)/(x + 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 9)/(x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(x + 4)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x - 9)/(x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 9)/(x + 11)] * [(2x + 8)/(x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 9)/(x + 11)] * [2]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(4x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(x + 2)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 7)/(4x - 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 7)/(4x - 7)] * [(x + 2)/(x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 7)/(4x - 7)] * [1]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(2x - 10),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(4x + 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 1)(2x + 9)/8(x - 5)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 1)/(2x - 10)] * [(2x + 9)/(4x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 1)/2(x - 5)] * [(2x + 9)/4(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 2)/(2x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(2x + 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "4(x - 1)(x + 5)/(2x + 11)(2x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 2)/(2x + 11)] * [(2x + 10)/(2x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 1)/(2x + 11)] * [2(x + 5)/(2x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 7)/(2x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/(3x + 4)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x - 7)(2x + 7)/(2x + 11)(3x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 7)/(2x + 11)] * [(2x + 7)/(3x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 7)/(2x + 11)] * [(2x + 7)/(3x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 7)/(x - 8),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(x + 2)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(4x - 7)(x + 5)/(x - 8)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 7)/(x - 8)] * [(2x + 10)/(x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x - 7)/(x - 8)] * [2(x + 5)/(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 1)/(4x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/(3x + 4)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 1)(2x + 7)/(4x + 5)(3x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 1)/(4x + 5)] * [(2x + 7)/(3x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 1)/(4x + 5)] * [(2x + 7)/(3x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 10)/(2x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 3)/(4x + 6)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(2x - 5)(x + 1)/(2x - 3)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 10)/(2x - 3)] * [(3x + 3)/(4x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x - 5)/(2x - 3)] * [3(x + 1)/2(2x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 8)/(x - 8),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 4)/(4x + 5)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x - 4)(x + 4)/(x - 8)(4x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 8)/(x - 8)] * [(x + 4)/(4x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 4)/(x - 8)] * [(x + 4)/(4x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 2)/(3x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(2x + 1)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 1)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 2)/(3x + 5)] * [(2x + 3)/(2x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 1)/(3x + 5)] * [(2x + 3)/(2x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 10)/(4x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 4)/(2x + 11)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 10)(x + 1)/(x - 1)(2x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 10)/(4x - 4)] * [(4x + 4)/(2x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 10)/4(x - 1)] * [4(x + 1)/(2x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 5)/(2x - 8),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(4x + 6)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x - 5)(x + 2)/4(x - 4)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 5)/(2x - 8)] * [(x + 2)/(4x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x - 5)/2(x - 4)] * [(x + 2)/2(2x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(3x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 3)/(4x + 11)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 1)/(3x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 11)/(3x + 11)] * [(3x + 3)/(4x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 11)/(3x + 11)] * [3(x + 1)/(4x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 1)/(x + 1)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 7)(3x + 1)/(4x + 1)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 7)/(4x + 1)] * [(3x + 1)/(x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 7)/(4x + 1)] * [(3x + 1)/(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 6)/(4x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/(3x + 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 2)(3x + 8)/(4x - 3)(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 6)/(4x - 3)] * [(3x + 8)/(3x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x + 2)/(4x - 3)] * [(3x + 8)/(3x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 9)/(x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 4)/(2x + 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "4(2x - 9)(x + 1)/(x + 3)(2x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 9)/(x + 3)] * [(4x + 4)/(2x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 9)/(x + 3)] * [4(x + 1)/(2x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 5)/(3x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(2x + 6)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 5)(2x + 9)/2(3x - 4)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 5)/(3x - 4)] * [(2x + 9)/(2x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 5)/(3x - 4)] * [(2x + 9)/2(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 5)/(4x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 6)/(3x + 10)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x - 5)(x + 6)/(4x + 11)(3x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 5)/(4x + 11)] * [(x + 6)/(3x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x - 5)/(4x + 11)] * [(x + 6)/(3x + 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 6)/(x + 2)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x + 3)(x + 6)/(x + 9)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 6)/(x + 9)] * [(x + 6)/(x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x + 3)/(x + 9)] * [(x + 6)/(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(2x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(4x + 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/4(2x - 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 2)/(2x - 1)] * [(2x + 3)/(4x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 2)/(2x - 1)] * [(2x + 3)/4(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 6)/(4x - 5),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(x + 10)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 6)(3x + 4)/(4x - 5)(x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 6)/(4x - 5)] * [(3x + 4)/(x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 6)/(4x - 5)] * [(3x + 4)/(x + 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(4x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(x + 5)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 11)/2(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 11)/(4x + 6)] * [(2x + 3)/(x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 11)/2(2x + 3)] * [(2x + 3)/(x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(2x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/(4x + 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 5)/(2x + 11)] * [(4x + 7)/(4x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 5)/(2x + 11)] * [1]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(4x - 10),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/(2x + 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 4)(4x + 7)/4(2x - 5)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 4)/(4x - 10)] * [(4x + 7)/(2x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 4)/2(2x - 5)] * [(4x + 7)/2(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(2x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 8)/(2x + 2)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 2)/(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 5)/(2x + 5)] * [(4x + 8)/(2x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[1] * [2(x + 2)/(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 10)/(x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(x + 4)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 10)(x + 2)/(x - 4)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 10)/(x - 4)] * [(x + 2)/(x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 10)/(x - 4)] * [(x + 2)/(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 8)/(x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 3)/(x + 4)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(3x - 8)(x + 1)/(x - 2)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 8)/(x - 2)] * [(3x + 3)/(x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 8)/(x - 2)] * [3(x + 1)/(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(2x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(x + 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 5)(3x + 10)/(x + 1)(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 10)/(2x + 2)] * [(3x + 10)/(x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 5)/(x + 1)] * [(3x + 10)/(x + 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/(3x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/(9x^2 + 15x - 6)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(3x + 2)(x + 2)/(3x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 2)/(3x - 1)] / [(3x + 8)/(9x^2 + 15x - 6)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 2)/(3x - 1)] * [(9x^2 + 15x - 6)/(3x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 2)/(3x - 1)] * [3(x + 2)(3x - 1)/(3x + 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 6)/(2x - 6),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(6x^2 - 16x - 6)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 6)(3x + 1)/(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 6)/(2x - 6)] / [(x + 1)/(6x^2 - 16x - 6)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 6)/(2x - 6)] * [(6x^2 - 16x - 6)/(x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 6)/2(x - 3)] * [2(3x + 1)(x - 3)/(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 4)/(2x^2 - 18)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 11)(x + 3)/(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 11)/(x - 3)] / [(2x + 4)/(2x^2 - 18)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 11)/(x - 3)] * [(2x^2 - 18)/(2x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 11)/(x - 3)] * [(x + 3)(x - 3)/(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 9)/(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 6)/(x + 2)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 9)/3(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 9)/(x + 2)] / [(3x + 6)/(x + 2)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 9)/(x + 2)] * [(x + 2)/(3x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 9)/(x + 2)] * [1/3]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 2)/(2x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(2x^2 + 10x - 28)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x - 1)(x + 7)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 2)/(2x - 4)] / [(2x + 3)/(2x^2 + 10x - 28)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 2)/(2x - 4)] * [(2x^2 + 10x - 28)/(2x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 1)/(x - 2)] * [2(x + 7)(x - 2)/(2x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 7)/(2x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(8x^2 + 40x + 48)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "4(4x - 7)(x + 2)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 7)/(2x + 6)] / [(3x + 4)/(8x^2 + 40x + 48)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 7)/(2x + 6)] * [(8x^2 + 40x + 48)/(3x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x - 7)/2(x + 3)] * [8(x + 2)(x + 3)/(3x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 2)/(4x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(12x^2 + 16x - 28)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 1)(3x + 7)/(x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 2)/(4x - 4)] / [(x + 7)/(12x^2 + 16x - 28)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 2)/(4x - 4)] * [(12x^2 + 16x - 28)/(x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 1)/2(x - 1)] * [4(3x + 7)(x - 1)/(x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (9x + 33)/(3x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 3)/(3x - 7)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 11)/(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(9x + 33)/(3x - 7)] / [(3x + 3)/(3x - 7)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(9x + 33)/(3x - 7)] * [(3x - 7)/(3x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(3x + 11)/(3x - 7)] * [(3x - 7)/3(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 8)/(x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 4)/(4x^2 + 29x + 30)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 4)(4x + 5)/(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 8)/(x + 6)] / [(2x + 4)/(4x^2 + 29x + 30)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 8)/(x + 6)] * [(4x^2 + 29x + 30)/(2x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 4)/(x + 6)] * [(x + 6)(4x + 5)/2(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(x^2 + 6x + 8)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 3)(x + 4)/2(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 9)/(x + 2)] / [(2x + 10)/(x^2 + 6x + 8)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 9)/(x + 2)] * [(x^2 + 6x + 8)/(2x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x + 3)/(x + 2)] * [(x + 2)(x + 4)/2(x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(3x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/(9x^2 - 6x - 35)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 9)(3x + 5)/(4x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 9)/(3x - 7)] / [(4x + 7)/(9x^2 - 6x - 35)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 9)/(3x - 7)] * [(9x^2 - 6x - 35)/(4x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 9)/(3x - 7)] * [(3x + 5)(3x - 7)/(4x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(3x + 10),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(3x + 10)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x + 3)/(3x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 6)/(3x + 10)] / [(3x + 10)/(3x + 10)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 6)/(3x + 10)] * [(3x + 10)/(3x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x + 3)/(3x + 10)] * [1]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 1)/(3x - 5),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(12x^2 - 8x - 20)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "4(x - 1)(x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 1)/(3x - 5)] / [(3x + 4)/(12x^2 - 8x - 20)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 1)/(3x - 5)] * [(12x^2 - 8x - 20)/(3x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 1)/(3x - 5)] * [4(x + 1)(3x - 5)/(3x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 8)/(4x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(16x^2 - 16x - 21)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 8)(4x + 3)/(4x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 8)/(4x - 7)] / [(4x + 1)/(16x^2 - 16x - 21)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 8)/(4x - 7)] * [(16x^2 - 16x - 21)/(4x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 8)/(4x - 7)] * [(4x + 3)(4x - 7)/(4x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (8x - 28)/(x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(x + 3)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "4(2x - 7)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(8x - 28)/(x + 3)] / [(3x + 5)/(x + 3)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(8x - 28)/(x + 3)] * [(x + 3)/(3x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(2x - 7)/(x + 3)] * [(x + 3)/(3x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 16)/(2x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(2x - 3)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 8)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 16)/(2x - 3)] / [(3x + 5)/(2x - 3)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 16)/(2x - 3)] * [(2x - 3)/(3x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 8)/(2x - 3)] * [(2x - 3)/(3x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 2)/(3x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(3x + 4)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x - 1)/(4x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 2)/(3x + 4)] / [(4x + 3)/(3x + 4)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 2)/(3x + 4)] * [(3x + 4)/(4x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x - 1)/(3x + 4)] * [(3x + 4)/(4x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 9)/(x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(4x^2 - 4x - 24)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "4(4x + 9)(x + 2)/(4x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 9)/(x - 3)] / [(4x + 1)/(4x^2 - 4x - 24)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 9)/(x - 3)] * [(4x^2 - 4x - 24)/(4x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 9)/(x - 3)] * [4(x + 2)(x - 3)/(4x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 2)/(2x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/(2x + 1)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 1)/(4x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 2)/(2x + 1)] / [(4x + 5)/(2x + 1)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 2)/(2x + 1)] * [(2x + 1)/(4x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 1)/(2x + 1)] * [(2x + 1)/(4x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 4)/(3x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 6)/(12x^2 - 5x - 2)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 4)(4x + 1)/2(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 4)/(3x - 2)] / [(2x + 6)/(12x^2 - 5x - 2)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 4)/(3x - 2)] * [(12x^2 - 5x - 2)/(2x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 4)/(3x - 2)] * [(4x + 1)(3x - 2)/2(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 9)/(4x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 1)/(12x^2 + 15x - 63)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "9(x - 3)(x + 3)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 9)/(4x - 7)] / [(3x + 1)/(12x^2 + 15x - 63)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 9)/(4x - 7)] * [(12x^2 + 15x - 63)/(3x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x - 3)/(4x - 7)] * [3(x + 3)(4x - 7)/(3x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/(3x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(3x^2 + 33x + 30)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 2)(x + 10)/(x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 2)/(3x + 3)] / [(x + 9)/(3x^2 + 33x + 30)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 2)/(3x + 3)] * [(3x^2 + 33x + 30)/(x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 2)/3(x + 1)] * [3(x + 1)(x + 10)/(x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (8x - 8)/(x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/(x - 7)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "8(x - 1)/(4x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(8x - 8)/(x - 7)] / [(4x + 7)/(x - 7)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(8x - 8)/(x - 7)] * [(x - 7)/(4x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[8(x - 1)/(x - 7)] * [(x - 7)/(4x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (12x - 6)/(3x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 2)/(3x + 4)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(2x - 1)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(12x - 6)/(3x + 4)] / [(4x + 2)/(3x + 4)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(12x - 6)/(3x + 4)] * [(3x + 4)/(4x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[6(2x - 1)/(3x + 4)] * [(3x + 4)/2(2x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(3x + 10),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(12x^2 + 46x + 20)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 9)(2x + 1)/(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 9)/(3x + 10)] / [(2x + 8)/(12x^2 + 46x + 20)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 9)/(3x + 10)] * [(12x^2 + 46x + 20)/(2x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 9)/(3x + 10)] * [(2x + 1)(3x + 10)/(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 10)/(3x - 10),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(12x^2 - 34x - 20)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x - 10)(2x + 1)/(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 10)/(3x - 10)] / [(x + 3)/(12x^2 - 34x - 20)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 10)/(3x - 10)] * [(12x^2 - 34x - 20)/(x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 10)/(3x - 10)] * [2(2x + 1)(3x - 10)/(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(2x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(2x^2 + 15x - 8)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 9)(x + 8)/(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 9)/(2x - 1)] / [(x + 2)/(2x^2 + 15x - 8)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 9)/(2x - 1)] * [(2x^2 + 15x - 8)/(x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 9)/(2x - 1)] * [(x + 8)(2x - 1)/(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(4x^2 + 31x + 21)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 1)(4x + 3)/(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 1)/(x + 7)] / [(x + 5)/(4x^2 + 31x + 21)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 1)/(x + 7)] * [(4x^2 + 31x + 21)/(x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 1)/(x + 7)] * [(x + 7)(4x + 3)/(x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (12x - 4)/(2x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 2)/(2x + 5)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(3x - 1)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(12x - 4)/(2x + 5)] / [(4x + 2)/(2x + 5)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(12x - 4)/(2x + 5)] * [(2x + 5)/(4x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(3x - 1)/(2x + 5)] * [(2x + 5)/2(2x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 3)/(4x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/(4x^2 + 48x + 44)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(4x - 3)(x + 11)/(2x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 3)/(4x + 4)] / [(2x + 7)/(4x^2 + 48x + 44)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 3)/(4x + 4)] * [(4x^2 + 48x + 44)/(2x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x - 3)/4(x + 1)] * [4(x + 1)(x + 11)/(2x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 3)/(4x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(16x^2 - 20x - 14)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(4x - 3)(2x + 1)/(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 3)/(4x - 7)] / [(2x + 8)/(16x^2 - 20x - 14)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 3)/(4x - 7)] * [(16x^2 - 20x - 14)/(2x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x - 3)/(4x - 7)] * [(2x + 1)(4x - 7)/(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 3)/(2x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 1)/(8x^2 - 14x - 49)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 1)(4x + 7)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 3)/(2x - 7)] / [(3x + 1)/(8x^2 - 14x - 49)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 3)/(2x - 7)] * [(8x^2 - 14x - 49)/(3x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x + 1)/(2x - 7)] * [(4x + 7)(2x - 7)/(3x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 4)/(4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 10)/(4x^2 + 25x + 6)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x - 4)(x + 6)/2(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 4)/(4x + 1)] / [(4x + 10)/(4x^2 + 25x + 6)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 4)/(4x + 1)] * [(4x^2 + 25x + 6)/(4x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 4)/(4x + 1)] * [(x + 6)(4x + 1)/2(2x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (12x - 40)/(4x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(4x - 3)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "4(3x - 10)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(12x - 40)/(4x - 3)] / [(2x + 1)/(4x - 3)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(12x - 40)/(4x - 3)] * [(4x - 3)/(2x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(3x - 10)/(4x - 3)] * [(4x - 3)/(2x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 6)/(4x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(16x^2 + 36x + 20)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "8(x - 3)(x + 1)/(x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 6)/(4x + 5)] / [(x + 11)/(16x^2 + 36x + 20)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 6)/(4x + 5)] * [(16x^2 + 36x + 20)/(x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 3)/(4x + 5)] * [4(x + 1)(4x + 5)/(x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(2x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/(2x^2 + 22x + 48)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 10)(x + 8)/(2x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 10)/(2x + 6)] / [(2x + 7)/(2x^2 + 22x + 48)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 10)/(2x + 6)] * [(2x^2 + 22x + 48)/(2x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 10)/2(x + 3)] * [2(x + 3)(x + 8)/(2x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(2x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 8)/(2x^2 + 26x + 72)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 1)(x + 9)/4(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 1)/(2x + 8)] / [(4x + 8)/(2x^2 + 26x + 72)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 1)/(2x + 8)] * [(2x^2 + 26x + 72)/(4x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 1)/2(x + 4)] * [(x + 4)(x + 9)/2(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(x - 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(x^2 + x - 30)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 5)(x + 6)/(x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 5)/(x - 5)] / [(x + 7)/(x^2 + x - 30)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 5)/(x - 5)] * [(x^2 + x - 30)/(x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 5)/(x - 5)] * [(x + 6)(x - 5)/(x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 4)/(3x + 10),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 10)/(3x^2 + 22x + 40)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 1)(x + 4)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 4)/(3x + 10)] / [(4x + 10)/(3x^2 + 22x + 40)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 4)/(3x + 10)] * [(3x^2 + 22x + 40)/(4x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(x + 1)/(3x + 10)] * [(x + 4)(3x + 10)/2(2x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 6)/(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 2)/(x^2 + 12x + 20)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 3)(x + 10)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 6)/(x + 2)] / [(4x + 2)/(x^2 + 12x + 20)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 6)/(x + 2)] * [(x^2 + 12x + 20)/(4x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 3)/(x + 2)] * [(x + 2)(x + 10)/2(2x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(4x - 8),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/(4x - 8)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 5)/(2x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 10)/(4x - 8)] / [(2x + 7)/(4x - 8)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 10)/(4x - 8)] * [(4x - 8)/(2x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 5)/2(x - 2)] * [4(x - 2)/(2x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 7)/(3x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 3)/(6x^2 + 16x - 6)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x - 7)(x + 3)/3(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 7)/(3x - 1)] / [(3x + 3)/(6x^2 + 16x - 6)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 7)/(3x - 1)] * [(6x^2 + 16x - 6)/(3x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 7)/(3x - 1)] * [2(x + 3)(3x - 1)/3(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 5)/(2x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 10)/(2x^2 + 25x + 33)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x - 5)(x + 11)/2(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 5)/(2x + 3)] / [(4x + 10)/(2x^2 + 25x + 33)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 5)/(2x + 3)] * [(2x^2 + 25x + 33)/(4x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 5)/(2x + 3)] * [(x + 11)(2x + 3)/2(2x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(x - 7)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 1)/(x - 7)] / [(3x + 10)/(x - 7)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 1)/(x - 7)] * [(x - 7)/(3x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 1)/(x - 7)] * [(x - 7)/(3x + 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 2)/(2x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(8x^2 - 4x - 4)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(3x - 2)(2x + 1)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 2)/(2x - 2)] / [(3x + 5)/(8x^2 - 4x - 4)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 2)/(2x - 2)] * [(8x^2 - 4x - 4)/(3x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 2)/2(x - 1)] * [4(2x + 1)(x - 1)/(3x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 6)/(2x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 2)/(8x^2 - 10x - 12)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(4x + 3)(x - 2)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 6)/(2x - 4)] / [(3x + 2)/(8x^2 - 10x - 12)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 6)/(2x - 4)] * [(8x^2 - 10x - 12)/(3x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3/2] * [2(4x + 3)(x - 2)/(3x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 10)/(4x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(16x^2 + 40x + 16)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "8(2x + 5)(x + 2)/(4x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 10)/(4x + 2)] / [(4x + 11)/(16x^2 + 40x + 16)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 10)/(4x + 2)] * [(16x^2 + 40x + 16)/(4x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)] * [8(x + 2)(2x + 1)/(4x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 10)/(x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/(4x^2 + 23x + 15)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x + 5)(4x + 3)/(4x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 10)/(x + 5)] / [(4x + 7)/(4x^2 + 23x + 15)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 10)/(x + 5)] * [(4x^2 + 23x + 15)/(4x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x + 5)/(x + 5)] * [(x + 5)(4x + 3)/(4x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 1)/(2x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/(6x^2 + 32x + 42)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 1)(3x + 7)/(2x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 1)/(2x + 6)] / [(2x + 7)/(6x^2 + 32x + 42)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 1)/(2x + 6)] * [(6x^2 + 32x + 42)/(2x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 1)/2(x + 3)] * [2(x + 3)(3x + 7)/(2x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 1)/(2x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(2x^2 + 16x + 30)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x - 1)(x + 5)/(4x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 1)/(2x + 6)] / [(4x + 11)/(2x^2 + 16x + 30)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 1)/(2x + 6)] * [(2x^2 + 16x + 30)/(4x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 1)/2(x + 3)] * [2(x + 3)(x + 5)/(4x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 2)/(4x + 10),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(12x^2 + 62x + 80)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x + 1)(3x + 8)/(2x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 2)/(4x + 10)] / [(2x + 11)/(12x^2 + 62x + 80)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 2)/(4x + 10)] * [(12x^2 + 62x + 80)/(2x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 1)/(2x + 5)] * [2(2x + 5)(3x + 8)/(2x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 9)/(3x - 10),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(3x^2 + 11x - 70)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x - 9)(x + 7)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 9)/(3x - 10)] / [(3x + 5)/(3x^2 + 11x - 70)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 9)/(3x - 10)] * [(3x^2 + 11x - 70)/(3x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 9)/(3x - 10)] * [(x + 7)(3x - 10)/(3x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 6)/(3x - 9),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 8)/(12x^2 - 21x - 45)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 6)(4x + 5)/(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 6)/(3x - 9)] / [(x + 8)/(12x^2 - 21x - 45)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 6)/(3x - 9)] * [(12x^2 - 21x - 45)/(x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 6)/3(x - 3)] * [3(4x + 5)(x - 3)/(x + 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 3)/(2x - 6),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(2x - 6)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 1)/(4x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 3)/(2x - 6)] / [(4x + 1)/(2x - 6)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 3)/(2x - 6)] * [(2x - 6)/(4x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x + 1)/2(x - 3)] * [2(x - 3)/(4x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 4)/(3x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(6x^2 + 18x - 24)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 4)(x + 4)/(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 4)/(3x - 3)] / [(3x + 7)/(6x^2 + 18x - 24)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 4)/(3x - 3)] * [(6x^2 + 18x - 24)/(3x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 4)/3(x - 1)] * [6(x + 4)(x - 1)/(3x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 7)/(4x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(4x^2 + 45x + 11)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x - 7)(x + 11)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 7)/(4x + 1)] / [(3x + 5)/(4x^2 + 45x + 11)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 7)/(4x + 1)] * [(4x^2 + 45x + 11)/(3x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 7)/(4x + 1)] * [(x + 11)(4x + 1)/(3x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 9)/(2x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 2)/(2x^2 + 13x + 21)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(4x - 9)(x + 3)/2(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 9)/(2x + 7)] / [(4x + 2)/(2x^2 + 13x + 21)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 9)/(2x + 7)] * [(2x^2 + 13x + 21)/(4x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x - 9)/(2x + 7)] * [(x + 3)(2x + 7)/2(2x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 1)/(4x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 6)/(4x^2 + 35x + 66)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(2x - 1)(x + 6)/3(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 1)/(4x + 11)] / [(3x + 6)/(4x^2 + 35x + 66)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 1)/(4x + 11)] * [(4x^2 + 35x + 66)/(3x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 1)/(4x + 11)] * [(x + 6)(4x + 11)/3(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (12x - 9)/(4x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(4x - 4)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "3(4x - 3)/(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(12x - 9)/(4x - 4)] / [(3x + 7)/(4x - 4)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(12x - 9)/(4x - 4)] * [(4x - 4)/(3x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(4x - 3)/4(x - 1)] * [4(x - 1)/(3x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 10)/(4x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(12x^2 + 50x + 22)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x - 10)(3x + 11)/3(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 10)/(4x + 2)] / [(3x + 9)/(12x^2 + 50x + 22)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 10)/(4x + 2)] * [(12x^2 + 50x + 22)/(3x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 10)/2(2x + 1)] * [2(2x + 1)(3x + 11)/3(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(2x^2 + 4x + 2)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 1)(x + 1)/(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 1)/(x + 1)] / [(2x + 8)/(2x^2 + 4x + 2)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x + 1)/(x + 1)] * [(2x^2 + 4x + 2)/(2x + 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[1] * [(x + 1)(x + 1)/(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 10)/(2x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 6)/(2x^2 + 11x + 5)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 10)(x + 5)/3(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 10)/(2x + 1)] / [(3x + 6)/(2x^2 + 11x + 5)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(x - 10)/(2x + 1)] * [(2x^2 + 11x + 5)/(3x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 10)/(2x + 1)] * [(x + 5)(2x + 1)/3(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 6)/(x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 10)/(x^2 + 18x + 81)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(x - 3)(x + 9)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 6)/(x + 9)] / [(4x + 10)/(x^2 + 18x + 81)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 6)/(x + 9)] * [(x^2 + 18x + 81)/(4x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 3)/(x + 9)] * [(x + 9)(x + 9)/2(2x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 2)/(4x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 6)/(16x^2 + 40x + 9)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "(3x - 2)(4x + 1)/2(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 2)/(4x + 9)] / [(2x + 6)/(16x^2 + 40x + 9)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 2)/(4x + 9)] * [(16x^2 + 40x + 9)/(2x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 2)/(4x + 9)] * [(4x + 1)(4x + 9)/2(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (16x - 28)/(x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 7)/(x + 1)\nFind (f / g)(x)", "answer": "4(4x - 7)/(2x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function division property, (f / g)(x) \u003d f(x) / g(x)\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(16x - 28)/(x + 1)] / [(2x + 7)/(x + 1)]\nFlip the divisor\n(f / g)(x) \u003d [(16x - 28)/(x + 1)] * [(x + 1)/(2x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(4x - 7)/(x + 1)] * [(x + 1)/(2x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f / g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 10)/(2x - 5),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(6x^2 - 24x - 30)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/3(2x - 5)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 10)/(2x - 5)] * [(3x + 5)/(6x^2 - 24x - 30)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 5)/(2x - 5)] * [(3x + 5)/6(x + 1)(x - 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 8)/(3x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(16x^2 + 64x + 64)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 3)/4(3x - 2)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 8)/(3x - 2)] * [(3x + 9)/(16x^2 + 64x + 64)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(x + 2)/(3x - 2)] * [3(x + 3)/16(x + 2)(x + 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(3x - 9),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(3x^2 + 24x + 21)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 3)/9(x - 3)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 7)/(3x - 9)] * [(x + 3)/(3x^2 + 24x + 21)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 7)/3(x - 3)] * [(x + 3)/3(x + 1)(x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(2x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(2x^2 + 16x + 14)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/4(x + 3)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 7)/(2x + 6)] * [(2x + 5)/(2x^2 + 16x + 14)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 7)/2(x + 3)] * [(2x + 5)/2(x + 1)(x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 2)/(4x - 10),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 3)/(3x - 2)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 1)/2(2x - 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 2)/(4x - 10)] * [(3x + 3)/(3x - 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 2)/2(2x - 5)] * [3(x + 1)/(3x - 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(3x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 6)/(16x^2 + 24x + 5)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 6)/(3x - 4)(4x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 1)/(3x - 4)] * [(x + 6)/(16x^2 + 24x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 1)/(3x - 4)] * [(x + 6)/(4x + 1)(4x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(2x - 10),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(6x^2 + 35x + 11)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 3)/2(x - 5)(3x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 11)/(2x - 10)] * [(3x + 9)/(6x^2 + 35x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 11)/2(x - 5)] * [3(x + 3)/(2x + 11)(3x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 10)/(2x - 8),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(6x^2 - 12x - 90)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/3(x - 4)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 10)/(2x - 8)] * [(4x + 6)/(6x^2 - 12x - 90)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 5)/(x - 4)] * [(2x + 3)/3(x + 3)(x - 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 18)/(2x - 6),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/(x - 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 5)/(x - 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 18)/(2x - 6)] * [(4x + 5)/(x - 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 9)/(x - 3)] * [(4x + 5)/(x - 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(6x^2 + 32x + 10)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 11)/(x - 4)(3x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 10)/(x - 4)] * [(3x + 11)/(6x^2 + 32x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 5)/(x - 4)] * [(3x + 11)/2(x + 5)(3x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 6)/(2x + 10),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 8)/(6x^2 + 18x - 60)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 2)/(x + 5)(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 6)/(2x + 10)] * [(4x + 8)/(6x^2 + 18x - 60)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x - 2)/2(x + 5)] * [2(x + 2)/3(x + 5)(x - 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 8)/(x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 9)/(16x^2 + 68x + 72)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 9)/(x + 1)(4x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 8)/(x + 1)] * [(2x + 9)/(16x^2 + 68x + 72)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(x + 2)/(x + 1)] * [(2x + 9)/4(x + 2)(4x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(3x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(12x^2 + 58x + 60)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 3)/2(3x - 7)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 10)/(3x - 7)] * [(3x + 9)/(12x^2 + 58x + 60)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 10)/(3x - 7)] * [3(x + 3)/2(2x + 3)(3x + 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 10)/(4x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 4)/(2x^2 + 8x - 90)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "4(x + 1)/(4x - 1)(x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 10)/(4x - 1)] * [(4x + 4)/(2x^2 + 8x - 90)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 5)/(4x - 1)] * [2(x + 1)/(x + 9)(x - 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 3)/(x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 5)/(3x^2 + 33x + 30)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(x - 2)(x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 3)/(x - 2)] * [(2x + 5)/(3x^2 + 33x + 30)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x + 1)/(x - 2)] * [(2x + 5)/3(x + 1)(x + 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 6)/(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(x^2 + 17x + 66)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x + 3)/(x + 2)(x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 6)/(x + 2)] * [(4x + 6)/(x^2 + 17x + 66)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 6)/(x + 2)] * [2(2x + 3)/(x + 6)(x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 1)/(2x - 5),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(2x^2 + 2x - 4)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/2(2x - 5)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 1)/(2x - 5)] * [(3x + 5)/(2x^2 + 2x - 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 1)/(2x - 5)] * [(3x + 5)/2(x + 2)(x - 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 4)/(4x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 10)/(2x - 4)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x + 5)/(4x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 4)/(4x + 11)] * [(4x + 10)/(2x - 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 2)/(4x + 11)] * [(2x + 5)/(x - 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 7)/(3x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(9x^2 + 12x - 77)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/(3x + 1)(3x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 7)/(3x + 1)] * [(2x + 3)/(9x^2 + 12x - 77)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 7)/(3x + 1)] * [(2x + 3)/(3x + 11)(3x - 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 2)/(3x - 9),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(8x^2 + 18x + 10)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 9)/3(x - 3)(4x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 2)/(3x - 9)] * [(x + 9)/(8x^2 + 18x + 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 1)/3(x - 3)] * [(x + 9)/2(x + 1)(4x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 10)/(x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(2x + 5)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(3x + 7)/(x - 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 10)/(x - 3)] * [(3x + 7)/(2x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x + 5)/(x - 3)] * [(3x + 7)/(2x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 3)/(3x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(4x^2 + 29x - 24)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/(3x + 8)(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 3)/(3x + 8)] * [(2x + 3)/(4x^2 + 29x - 24)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x - 3)/(3x + 8)] * [(2x + 3)/(x + 8)(4x - 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(6x^2 + 32x + 32)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 11)/2(x - 1)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 4)/(x - 1)] * [(2x + 11)/(6x^2 + 32x + 32)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 4)/(x - 1)] * [(2x + 11)/2(x + 4)(3x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(2x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(16x^2 + 68x + 66)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 3)/(2x - 7)(4x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 6)/(2x - 7)] * [(x + 3)/(16x^2 + 68x + 66)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x + 3)/(2x - 7)] * [(x + 3)/2(2x + 3)(4x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 5)/(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 8)/(12x^2 + 25x - 50)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 8)/(x + 2)(3x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 5)/(x + 2)] * [(x + 8)/(12x^2 + 25x - 50)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x - 5)/(x + 2)] * [(x + 8)/(3x + 10)(4x - 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 7)/(3x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(3x - 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 4)/(3x - 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 7)/(3x - 1)] * [(2x + 8)/(3x - 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 7)/(3x - 1)] * [2(x + 4)/(3x - 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 4)/(4x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 2)/(x + 1)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "8(x + 1)/(4x - 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 4)/(4x - 1)] * [(2x + 2)/(x + 1)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(x + 1)/(4x - 1)] * [2]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (6x - 18)/(2x - 9),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(3x - 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(4x + 11)/(2x - 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(6x - 18)/(2x - 9)] * [(4x + 11)/(3x - 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[6(x - 3)/(2x - 9)] * [(4x + 11)/3(x - 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(4x - 10),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 6)/(6x^2 + 21x + 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 2)/2(2x - 5)(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 9)/(4x - 10)] * [(3x + 6)/(6x^2 + 21x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x + 3)/2(2x - 5)] * [(x + 2)/(x + 3)(2x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(4x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(8x^2 + 34x + 33)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 3)/(4x - 1)(4x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 3)/(4x - 1)] * [(x + 3)/(8x^2 + 34x + 33)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 3)/(4x - 1)] * [(x + 3)/(2x + 3)(4x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (12x - 24)/(x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 8)/(3x - 6)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "4(x + 8)/(x - 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(12x - 24)/(x - 7)] * [(x + 8)/(3x - 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[12(x - 2)/(x - 7)] * [(x + 8)/3(x - 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 6)/(4x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(8x^2 + 20x - 48)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/4(2x - 1)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 6)/(4x - 2)] * [(3x + 5)/(8x^2 + 20x - 48)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 3)/(2x - 1)] * [(3x + 5)/4(x + 4)(2x - 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 8)/(4x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 6)/(x^2 + x - 72)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 2)/2(2x + 1)(x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 8)/(4x + 2)] * [(3x + 6)/(x^2 + x - 72)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 8)/2(2x + 1)] * [3(x + 2)/(x + 9)(x - 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (12x - 32)/(4x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(3x - 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "4(2x + 3)/(4x - 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(12x - 32)/(4x - 1)] * [(2x + 3)/(3x - 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(3x - 8)/(4x - 1)] * [(2x + 3)/(3x - 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (6x + 6)/(4x + 3),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 7)/(3x + 3)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 7)/(4x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(6x + 6)/(4x + 3)] * [(x + 7)/(3x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[6(x + 1)/(4x + 3)] * [(x + 7)/3(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(3x - 9),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(3x^2 + 25x + 50)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/3(x - 3)(3x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 5)/(3x - 9)] * [(3x + 4)/(3x^2 + 25x + 50)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 5)/3(x - 3)] * [(3x + 4)/(x + 5)(3x + 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 4)/(x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(2x^2 + 12x - 32)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 11)/(x - 4)(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 4)/(x - 4)] * [(4x + 11)/(2x^2 + 12x - 32)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 2)/(x - 4)] * [(4x + 11)/2(x + 8)(x - 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 6)/(2x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(x + 3)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "4(x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 6)/(2x + 1)] * [(2x + 10)/(x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 3)/(2x + 1)] * [2(x + 5)/(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(2x - 5),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(8x^2 + 56x + 80)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 10)/4(2x - 5)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 10)/(2x - 5)] * [(3x + 10)/(8x^2 + 56x + 80)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 5)/(2x - 5)] * [(3x + 10)/8(x + 2)(x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 2)/(4x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(12x^2 + 14x - 10)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 9)/2(3x + 5)(2x - 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 2)/(4x - 2)] * [(x + 9)/(12x^2 + 14x - 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[1] * [(x + 9)/2(3x + 5)(2x - 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 18)/(2x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(2x - 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(3x + 11)/(2x - 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 18)/(2x - 3)] * [(3x + 11)/(2x - 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x - 9)/(2x - 3)] * [(3x + 11)/(2x - 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 4)/(2x - 6),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 10)/(3x^2 + 14x - 24)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 10)/2(x - 3)(x + 6)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 4)/(2x - 6)] * [(x + 10)/(3x^2 + 14x - 24)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 4)/2(x - 3)] * [(x + 10)/(x + 6)(3x - 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 3)/(2x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 1)/(2x^2 + x - 21)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 1)/(2x - 3)(2x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 3)/(2x - 3)] * [(4x + 1)/(2x^2 + x - 21)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 3)/(2x - 3)] * [(4x + 1)/(2x + 7)(x - 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 22)/(x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(2x + 11)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 11)/(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 22)/(x + 1)] * [(x + 11)/(2x + 11)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x + 11)/(x + 1)] * [(x + 11)/(2x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 16)/(3x - 6),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 6)/(2x - 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 2)/(x - 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 16)/(3x - 6)] * [(3x + 6)/(2x - 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(x - 4)/3(x - 2)] * [3(x + 2)/2(x - 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 5)/(4x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 10)/(8x^2 - 10x - 25)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 10)/2(2x + 3)(4x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 5)/(4x + 6)] * [(3x + 10)/(8x^2 - 10x - 25)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 5)/2(2x + 3)] * [(3x + 10)/(4x + 5)(2x - 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 5)/(2x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(6x^2 - 7x - 5)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 9)/(2x - 3)(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 5)/(2x - 3)] * [(x + 9)/(6x^2 - 7x - 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 5)/(2x - 3)] * [(x + 9)/(2x + 1)(3x - 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 5)/(x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(16x^2 - 25)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 9)/(x + 5)(4x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 5)/(x + 5)] * [(x + 9)/(16x^2 - 25)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x - 5)/(x + 5)] * [(x + 9)/(4x + 5)(4x - 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 8)/(x - 6),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/(2x^2 - 6x - 80)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 7)/2(x - 6)(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 8)/(x - 6)] * [(4x + 7)/(2x^2 - 6x - 80)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 8)/(x - 6)] * [(4x + 7)/2(x + 5)(x - 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(x + 6),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 1)/(16x^2 + 56x + 48)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/4(x + 6)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 6)/(x + 6)] * [(2x + 1)/(16x^2 + 56x + 48)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x + 3)/(x + 6)] * [(2x + 1)/8(x + 2)(2x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 7)/(2x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 7)/(3x^2 + 23x - 70)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 7)/(2x + 1)(x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 7)/(2x + 1)] * [(4x + 7)/(3x^2 + 23x - 70)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 7)/(2x + 1)] * [(4x + 7)/(x + 10)(3x - 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(2x - 9),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(4x^2 + 21x + 5)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x + 3)/(2x - 9)(4x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 5)/(2x - 9)] * [(4x + 6)/(4x^2 + 21x + 5)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 5)/(2x - 9)] * [2(2x + 3)/(x + 5)(4x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(4x - 6),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(3x^2 + 38x + 55)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 5)/2(2x - 3)(3x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 11)/(4x - 6)] * [(x + 5)/(3x^2 + 38x + 55)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 11)/2(2x - 3)] * [(x + 5)/(x + 11)(3x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (8x - 16)/(2x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(4x - 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(3x + 4)/(2x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(8x - 16)/(2x + 9)] * [(3x + 4)/(4x - 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[8(x - 2)/(2x + 9)] * [(3x + 4)/4(x - 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 10)/(3x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(4x^2 + 54x + 110)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 4)/(3x + 7)(x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 10)/(3x + 7)] * [(2x + 8)/(4x^2 + 54x + 110)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x + 5)/(3x + 7)] * [(x + 4)/(x + 11)(2x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 10)/(3x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/(x^2 - 4x - 60)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 8)/(3x - 4)(x + 6)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 10)/(3x - 4)] * [(3x + 8)/(x^2 - 4x - 60)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 10)/(3x - 4)] * [(3x + 8)/(x + 6)(x - 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 3)/(3x + 5),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(4x^2 + 14x + 12)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/2(3x + 5)(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)] * [(3x + 4)/(4x^2 + 14x + 12)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)] * [(3x + 4)/2(x + 2)(2x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 5)/(4x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 8)/(4x^2 + 19x - 30)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 8)/4(x - 1)(x + 6)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 5)/(4x - 4)] * [(x + 8)/(4x^2 + 19x - 30)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x - 5)/4(x - 1)] * [(x + 8)/(x + 6)(4x - 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 7)/(2x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 11)/(6x^2 - 11x - 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 11)/(2x + 1)(2x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 7)/(2x + 1)] * [(4x + 11)/(6x^2 - 11x - 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 7)/(2x + 1)] * [(4x + 11)/(2x + 1)(3x - 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (12x + 21)/(4x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 2)/(4x + 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "6(x + 1)/(4x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(12x + 21)/(4x + 9)] * [(2x + 2)/(4x + 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(4x + 7)/(4x + 9)] * [2(x + 1)/(4x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(2x + 10),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(8x^2 + 40x + 32)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 7)/8(x + 5)(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 8)/(2x + 10)] * [(3x + 7)/(8x^2 + 40x + 32)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 4)/(x + 5)] * [(3x + 7)/8(x + 1)(x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 10)/(4x - 8),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 4)/(4x^2 + 10x - 50)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 4)/4(x - 2)(x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 10)/(4x - 8)] * [(x + 4)/(4x^2 + 10x - 50)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 5)/2(x - 2)] * [(x + 4)/2(x + 5)(2x - 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 1)/(x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(x^2 + 10x + 9)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 11)/(x - 1)(x + 9)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 1)/(x - 1)] * [(3x + 11)/(x^2 + 10x + 9)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 1)/(x - 1)] * [(3x + 11)/(x + 1)(x + 9)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 2)/(3x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(4x^2 + 14x + 12)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/2(3x + 11)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 2)/(3x + 11)] * [(3x + 5)/(4x^2 + 14x + 12)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 2)/(3x + 11)] * [(3x + 5)/2(x + 2)(2x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 3)/(x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 5)/(4x + 3)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(4x + 5)/(x - 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 3)/(x - 3)] * [(4x + 5)/(4x + 3)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(4x + 3)/(x - 3)] * [(4x + 5)/(4x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 7)/(4x - 8),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(9x^2 + 33x + 28)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 9)/4(x - 2)(3x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 7)/(4x - 8)] * [(x + 9)/(9x^2 + 33x + 28)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 7)/4(x - 2)] * [(x + 9)/(3x + 4)(3x + 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 8)/(x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(6x^2 + 8x - 64)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 3)/2(x + 1)(x + 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 8)/(x + 1)] * [(x + 3)/(6x^2 + 8x - 64)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 8)/(x + 1)] * [(x + 3)/2(x + 4)(3x - 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 4)/(x + 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 9)/(4x^2 + 30x + 44)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 9)/(x + 2)(2x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 4)/(x + 2)] * [(x + 9)/(4x^2 + 30x + 44)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2] * [(x + 9)/2(x + 2)(2x + 11)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (6x + 6)/(x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 11)/(2x + 2)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(2x + 11)/(x + 8)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(6x + 6)/(x + 8)] * [(2x + 11)/(2x + 2)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[6(x + 1)/(x + 8)] * [(2x + 11)/2(x + 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 4)/(4x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 3)/(3x + 4)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 3)/(4x - 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 4)/(4x - 1)] * [(x + 3)/(3x + 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 4)/(4x - 1)] * [(x + 3)/(3x + 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 12)/(3x + 11),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(2x + 6)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 5)/(3x + 11)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 12)/(3x + 11)] * [(x + 5)/(2x + 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[4(x + 3)/(3x + 11)] * [(x + 5)/2(x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (16x - 16)/(x - 4),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 10)/(4x - 4)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "8(x + 5)/(x - 4)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(16x - 16)/(x - 4)] * [(2x + 10)/(4x - 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[16(x - 1)/(x - 4)] * [(x + 5)/2(x - 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 9)/(4x - 3),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 8)/(3x^2 + 21x - 90)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 8)/(4x - 3)(x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 9)/(4x - 3)] * [(3x + 8)/(3x^2 + 21x - 90)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x - 3)/(4x - 3)] * [(3x + 8)/3(x + 10)(x - 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 10)/(2x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 9)/(12x^2 + 10x - 100)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 3)/(2x + 7)(3x + 10)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 10)/(2x + 7)] * [(3x + 9)/(12x^2 + 10x - 100)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x - 5)/(2x + 7)] * [3(x + 3)/2(3x + 10)(2x - 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 2)/(4x - 5),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 1)/(12x^2 + 30x - 18)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/3(4x - 5)(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 2)/(4x - 5)] * [(3x + 1)/(12x^2 + 30x - 18)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(2x - 1)/(4x - 5)] * [(3x + 1)/6(x + 3)(2x - 1)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x - 8)/(4x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 11)/(6x^2 - 22x - 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 11)/(4x + 7)(3x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x - 8)/(4x + 7)] * [(3x + 11)/(6x^2 - 22x - 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x - 4)/(4x + 7)] * [(3x + 11)/2(3x + 1)(x - 4)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x - 14)/(4x + 4),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(2x - 7)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/(x + 1)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x - 14)/(4x + 4)] * [(4x + 6)/(2x - 7)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x - 7)/2(x + 1)] * [2(2x + 3)/(2x - 7)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (8x - 16)/(3x + 9),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 2)/(2x - 4)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "8(2x + 1)/3(x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(8x - 16)/(3x + 9)] * [(4x + 2)/(2x - 4)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[8(x - 2)/3(x + 3)] * [(2x + 1)/(x - 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 8)/(3x + 7),\ng(x) \u003d (4x + 10)/(3x - 8)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(2x + 5)/(3x + 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 8)/(3x + 7)] * [(4x + 10)/(3x - 8)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x - 8)/(3x + 7)] * [2(2x + 5)/(3x - 8)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(2x + 10),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(3x^2 + 23x + 30)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 4)/(x + 5)(x + 6)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x + 5)/(2x + 10)] * [(2x + 8)/(3x^2 + 23x + 30)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(3x + 5)/2(x + 5)] * [2(x + 4)/(x + 6)(3x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (4x + 6)/(4x + 8),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(4x^2 + 22x + 24)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "1/2(x + 2)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(4x + 6)/(4x + 8)] * [(2x + 8)/(4x^2 + 22x + 24)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(2x + 3)/2(x + 2)] * [1/(2x + 3)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x + 5)/(2x - 2),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(4x^2 + 30x + 50)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(x + 11)/4(x - 1)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x + 5)/(2x - 2)] * [(x + 11)/(4x^2 + 30x + 50)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x + 5)/2(x - 1)] * [(x + 11)/2(x + 5)(2x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (3x - 30)/(x - 7),\ng(x) \u003d (x + 11)/(x - 10)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "3(x + 11)/(x - 7)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(3x - 30)/(x - 7)] * [(x + 11)/(x - 10)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[3(x - 10)/(x - 7)] * [(x + 11)/(x - 10)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (2x + 8)/(2x + 1),\ng(x) \u003d (3x + 5)/(8x^2 + 42x + 40)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 1)(4x + 5)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(2x + 8)/(2x + 1)] * [(3x + 5)/(8x^2 + 42x + 40)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[2(x + 4)/(2x + 1)] * [(3x + 5)/2(x + 4)(4x + 5)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Given f(x) \u003d (x - 2)/(3x - 1),\ng(x) \u003d (2x + 6)/(4x^2 - 5x - 6)\nFind (f * g)(x)", "answer": "2(x + 3)/(3x - 1)(4x + 3)", "explanation": "By the function multiplication property, (f * g)(x) \u003d f(x) * g(x)\n(f * g)(x) \u003d [(x - 2)/(3x - 1)] * [(2x + 6)/(4x^2 - 5x - 6)]\nFactor the numerators and denominators of the rational expressions\n[(x - 2)/(3x - 1)] * [2(x + 3)/(4x + 3)(x - 2)]\nMultiply the numerators of the rational expressions together and the denominators of the rational expressions together\nDivide out any polynomials that are in both the numerator and denominator", "prompt": "(f * g)(x) \u003d"}
]}